<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile H1D023103</string>
    <string name="ball_menu">Club History</string>
    <string name="coach_menu">Head Coach</string>
    <string name="player_menu">Squad Teams</string>
    <string name="club_description">Moreirense Futebol Clube is a Portuguese professional football club based in Moreira de Cónegos, Guimarães Municipality, Minho. Founded on 1 November 1938, it plays in the Primeira Liga, holding home games at Parque de Jogos Comendador Joaquim de Almeida Freitas, with a capacity for 6,150 spectators.</string>
    <string name="club_history">Moreirense was founded in 1938. It first reached the Liga de Honra in 1995, where they stayed five seasons. After being relegated to Segunda Divisão, manager Manuel Machado took the team and, in two years, managed two promotions, getting the team for the first time to the top flight. He led the northerners for two more seasons, in which Moreirense achieved two mid-table positions, finishing ninth in the latter season.\n\nAfter Machado departed for neighbouring Vitória de Guimarães, the club suffered two consecutive relegations, only returning again to the second level in 2010, and the first in 2012. After an immediate relegation, the team won the 2013–14 Segunda Liga under manager Toni Conceição.\n\nMoreirense achieved its first top level national title on 29 January 2017, winning the League Cup (Taça da Liga) by defeating S.C. Braga in the final.\n\nIn 2018–19, manager Ivo Vieira led Moreirense to a best-ever sixth place, missing out on the fifth place only on goal difference to Vitória de Guimarães, who Vieira left the club for. Following two 8th-place finishes, the team were relegated in 2021–22, a season in which they had three managers: João Henriques, Lito Vidigal and Ricardo Sá Pinto. Relegation was confirmed with a 2–1 aggregate playoff loss to G.D. Chaves.\n\nUnder Paulo Alves, Moreirense instantly returned to the top flight by winning the 2022–23 Liga Portugal 2. The team took 79 points from a possible 102, the highest in an 18-team season of the league, and the highest percentage taken from any season of it. Alves left at the end of the season.</string>
    <string name="back">Kembali</string>
    <string name="no_data">Tidak Ada Data</string>
</resources>